Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- Mitra, Sanjit K. Immigration 1963 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Morse Telegraph-Correspondance, 1941-1961 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Morton, Dr. George (Box 91, Folder 14)
- N.S.F.- Secondary School Program Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Navy Enlisted Scientific Education Program, 1958-1962 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- M.E. Study, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Mechanics- Strength of Materials Sequence, 1957-1960 (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Mei, Chuh, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 19)
- Nutrition, School of Advisory Board, 1958-1973 (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Moyver, D.H. (Box 91, Folder 21)
- Muller, Steven VP Public Affairs (Box 91, Folder 22)
- "N", 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 23)
- News Bureau, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 24)
- NYS Accreditation Prof. Masters, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 25)
- New York State Advisory Council, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 26)
- NYS Assembly Scuentific Staff, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 27)
- NYS Education Department- Planning in Higher education (TV-Cashin), 1959-1970 (Box 91, Folder 28)
- NYS Science Foundation, 1961-71 (Box 91, Folder 29)
- "O", 1960-1963 (Box 91, Folder 30)
- "P-Q", 1960-1963 (Box 91, Folder 31)
- Peace Corps, 1961-1964 (Box 91, Folder 32)
- GA-GN, 1959-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- GO, 1958-1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Gallager, R.H., 1971-1977 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Garwin, Richard (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Gates, C.D., 1966-1976 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Gaver, Donald P. Jr., 1926 and 1965 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Gebhart, Benjamin, 1966-1981 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- General Electric Company to June 30, 1982, 1972-1982 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- General Electric Equipment Proposal, May, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- General Electric, 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- General Electric, 1961-1969 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- General Electric Equipment Gift Program, 1964-1965 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- General Electric, 1958-1961 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- General Electric Co. Professor's Conference, September 1960 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- G.E. Management Conference 7/23-27/72 Crontonville, N.Y., 1972 and 1974 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- General Telephone and Electronics, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- General Motors Corporation, 1987-1989 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- General Motor Corporation, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- General Motors Corporation, 1984-1985 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- General Motors Corporation, July 1, 1982-June 30, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- General Motor Corporation, July 1, 1978-June 20, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 21)
- General Motors Corporation, 1969-1979 (Box 92, Folder 22)
- Genesys Systems, Inc., 1972 (Box 92, Folder 23)
- General Electric Company, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 24)
- General Electric Company, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 25)
- General Electric Company, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 26)
- General Electric-CALMA Visit, September, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 27)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, June 1984-February 1986 (Box 92, Folder 28)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, June 1983-February 1984 (Box 92, Folder 29)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, February 1982 and June 1983 (Box 92, Folder 30)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, March 1980-February 1982 (Box 92, Folder 31)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, July 1978-March 1980 (Box 92, Folder 32)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, January 1977-June 1978 (Box 92, Folder 33)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, July 1975-December 1976 (Box 92, Folder 34)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, July 1973-June 1975 (Box 92, Folder 35)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, January 1972-May 1973 (Box 92, Folder 36)
- Geological Sciences, Department of, December 1970-December 1971 (Box 92, Folder 37)
- Geological Sciences Building, 1981 and 1983 (Box 92, Folder 38)
- Geological Sciences Building, March 1981 (Box 92, Folder 39)
- Geological Sciences Building, June 1980-February 1981 (Box 92, Folder 40)
- Geological Sciences Building 4/1980-7/1979, 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 41)
- Associate Dean Geological Sciences, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 42)
- Associate Dean Geological Sciences, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 43)
- Geological Sciences, Department of History of bringing Geology from Arts into Engineering, 1969-1972 (Box 92, Folder 44)
- Geology (ENG'G) and Geo Technical ENG'G, 1965-1970 (Box 92, Folder 45)
- Gift Reports to July 1, 1984, 1970-1984 (Box 92, Folder 46)
- Glenmede Trust Company to July 1, 1980, 1972-1979 (Box 92, Folder 47)
- Government Affairs, Office of July 1, 1987 to June 30, 1989, 1985-1988 (Box 92, Folder 48)
- Government, U.S. (Letters to Congressmen, Senators re educational cut backs etc.), 1982-1984 (Box 92, Folder 49)
- Gradung-Grade Distribution and SU Grading July 1, 1972, 1974 and 1977 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Grading 1960-June, 1972, 1962-1970 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Grading System, 1959 and 1961 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Graduate Activities, 1964 and 1968 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Graduate Aid Study, 1958 and 1960 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Grad, Assistants Labor Relations, 1970 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Graduate Committee Engineering Division, 1959-1962 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Government Affairs, Office of Stephen Johnson Director to July 1, 1987, 1985-1987 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Graduate Professional Masters Degree Program July 1, 1983- June 30, 1988, 1965-1988 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Graduate Professional Masters Degree Program July 1, 1976- June 30, 1983, 1975-1983 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Graduate Professional Program Committee 1965-June 30, 1975, 1965-1975 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Graduate School 1973-1/1982, 1973-1982 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Graduate School 1970-1972, 1966-1972 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Graduate School, 1961-1965 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Graduate School, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Graduate School of Nutrition- Administrative Board, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Graduate Student Bargaining Comm., 1970 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- GunLocke, H.W., 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Guralnick, Sidney A., Dr., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- H: HA-HE, 1965-1970 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- HI-HO, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Hardin, George, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 22)
- Hatfield, Robert, Fellowship Program To July 1, 1987, 1982-1985 (Box 93, Folder 23)
- HEOP Program, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 24)
- Hewlett-Packard Company, July 1, 1982-June 30, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 25)
- Hewlett-Packard Company To July 1, 1982, 1978-1982 (Box 93, Folder 26)
- High Voltage Microscope, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 27)
- Hollister's Report on College of Engineering, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 28)
- Hollister S.C., 1937-1980 (Box 93, Folder 29)
- Honors Program, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 30)
- Honors Program, 1960-1970 (Box 93, Folder 31)
- Hopkins, Vivianc, 1976-1978 (Box 93, Folder 32)
- Howe, John P., 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 33)
- Human Affairs Program, 1971-1975 (Box 93, Folder 34)
- Humphrey, Arthur E., 1969 and 1973 (Box 93, Folder 35)
- Hydraulics-Hydrology Professorship, 1961-1963 (Box 93, Folder 36)
- I, 1959-1964 (Box 93, Folder 37)
- I.B.M., July 1, 1985-January 1, 1989 (Box 93, Folder 38)
- I.B.M., December 21, 1984-June 30, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 39)
- I.B.M., July 8, 1982-December 21, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 40)
- I.B.M., July 1, 1981-July 8, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 41)
- I.B.M. to July 1,1981, 1975-1981 (Box 93, Folder 42)
- I.B.M., 1974-1979 (Box 93, Folder 43)
- I.B.M., 1966 and 1973 (Box 93, Folder 44)
- I.B.M. Proposals, 1980-1983 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- I.B.M. Research Triangle Park, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Industrial Education Program, 1959 and 1961 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Industrial ENG'g (A.S.Jr.), 1962-1972 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Industrial ENGR. and Operations research, January 1965-July 1975 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Industrial Engr. and Operation research, July 1960-January 1963 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- I.E. Recommendations General, 1963-1965 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Industrial Innovation Extension, April-June 1987 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Industrial Innovation, June 1, 1985-March 31, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Industrial Liaison, 1967-1969 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Industrial Liaison (Associates-Gordon), 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Industrial Research Park Cornell University, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Information Study, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- INGERsoll-Rand CO., 1979 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Ionosphere Radar Project, 1958-1959 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Inquiries Re C.U. Engineering, 1968 and 1970 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Institute of Elect. and Electronic Engineers, 1964-1974 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- International Education Program, 1964-1970 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- International-Ecole Natl. Sup. de Aero, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- International Foreign Students on Campus Programs, 1966-1969 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- International Proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 21)
- International Studies ad hoc Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- Center for International Studies, July 1, 1983-June 30, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 23)
- International Studies Center for, 1962-1972 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Intersession 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 25)
- Ireland IE Conference 1966 and ensuing Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 94, Folder 26)
- I.R.I., 1966 (Box 94, Folder 27)
- IRRPOS, 1969-1971 (Box 94, Folder 28)
- Isard, Walter, 1973-1980 (Box 94, Folder 29)
- ITAR/EAR, 1982-1984 (Box 94, Folder 30)
- ITAR/EAR, 1981-1982 (Box 94, Folder 31)
- Jackson, R. Peter, 1968-1973 (Box 94, Folder 32)
- Jackson State University, 1979-1981 (Box 94, Folder 33)
- JAPAN, 1974-1983 (Box 94, Folder 34)
- Jelinck, Fredrick, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 35)
- Johnson, Andrew R., 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 36)
- Johnson, David Admissions, 1974-1982 (Box 94, Folder 37)
- Junior Year Abroad, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 38)
- Kennedy, W. Keith, 1970-1978 (Box 94, Folder 39)
- Kimball-Thurston Donors, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 40)
- Knight, Lester B. and Associates, July 1, 1979-June 30, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 41)
- Kodak Eastman Company, 1973-1983 (Box 94, Folder 42)
- Koppers Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 94, Folder 43)
- Krauter, Allan I., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 44)
- Kroner, E., 1966 (Box 94, Folder 45)
- Ku, Walter, 1976-1984 (Box 94, Folder 46)
- Knight, Lester B. Associates, Inc., 1964-1979 (Box 94, Folder 47)
- Laboratory Work in Engineering, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 48)
- Lake, Charles W. Lake, Jr. Chair in Productivity-Search Committee for, 1944-1985 (Box 94, Folder 49)
- Keast Committees, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 50)
- Lake, Charles W. to July 1, 1987, 1965-1985 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Lake, Charles W., Jr. Chair in Productivity Announcement, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Lance, Richard H., 1976-1985 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Land Grant Aspects, 1975-1980 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Land Grant Centennial, 1959-1960 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Latin American Year, 1964-1965 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Lawrence, Samuel A.-VP Adm., 1970-1976 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Lea, Robert B. People to People Program, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Librarian, Review of University, 1981-1984 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Libraries, 1954-1981 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Libraries University, 1970-1979 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Libraries, Cornell University Integrated Library System, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Library Committee, Engineering, 1971-1982 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Library, John M. Olin, 1961 and 1965 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- James F. Lincoln Arc Welding Foundation, 1949-1958 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Link Aviation, 1959-1960 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Littlewood, William, 1959-1967 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- Long, Dr. F.A., 1964-1969 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Long Range Planning Committee, 1962 and 1968 (Box 95, Folder 20)
- Lucas, William F., 1971-1984 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- Ludford, G.S.S., 1977-1981 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Materials Science and Engineering, January 1, 1988-June 30, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- Loucks, Daniel P., 1979-1981 (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Lukens Steel Co., 1956-1960 (Box 95, Folder 25)
- L.U.N.R., 1971 (Box 95, Folder 26)
- Lykoudis, Paul S., 1961-1977 (Box 95, Folder 27)
- Lyon, George B. Prof, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 28)
- McGarrah, Robert E., 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 29)
- McLain, Norman, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 30)
- McFadden, 1956-1957 (Box 95, Folder 31)
- McFarlane, Ross, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 32)
- McKeegan, Paul, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 33)
- McKersie, Robert Dean, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 34)
- McManus, Howard N., Jr., 1971-1977 (Box 95, Folder 35)
- McManus, John F., 1980-1981 (Box 95, Folder 36)
- McNair, Arthur, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 37)
- Mackesey T.W., 1964-1971 (Box 95, Folder 38)
- Manhatten College, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 39)
- Master Plan, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 40)
- Materials and Mechanics, 1957-1961 (Box 95, Folder 41)
- Materials Processing, 1961-1964 (Box 95, Folder 42)
- Materials Processing Study, 1966-1970 (Box 95, Folder 43)
- Materials Science and Engineering, January 1, 1987-June 30, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 44)
- Materials Science and Engineering Dept., January 1, 1986-June 30, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 45)
- Liberal Studies, 1961-1966 (Box 95, Folder 46)
- Biographical Material on John McManus, Dean, 1948-1980 (Box 96)
- Electrical Engineering (1), 1996-1997 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Electrical Engineering (2), 1996-1997 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Dick, Richard, 1977-1988 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Electrical Engineering, 1998-1999 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Electrical Engineering Program Review, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Electronic Packaging Alliance, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Dual Degree Option, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Bangs Lecture Material, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Duffield Hall, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- DuPont, E.I. de Nemours & Co., 1967-2000 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Earth Day, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Tau Beta Pi (starting July 1, 1985), 1998 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- National Engineering Action Conference, April 7, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Mechanical & Aerospace Engineering, School of, July 1, 1985-June 30, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Materials Science & Engineering, Dept. of, July 1,1984 -June 30, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 15)
- Microelectronics Center of North Carolina, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 16)
- Microscopy Study, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 17)
- Middle States Accreditation, 1968-1979 (Box 97, Folder 18)
- Minority Programs to 30 June 1988 (Box 97, Folder 19)
- Minority Education, 1970-1980 (Box 97, Folder 20)
- Miley, George, 1976-1978 (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Minn. Mining & Mfg. Co. (3M), 1968-1971 (Box 97, Folder 22)
- Mohawk Valley Community College visit ASEE, 15 April 1969 (Box 97, Folder 23)
- Moore, Harriet- Farewell Reception, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 24)
- Moore, Franklin K., 1972-1974 (Box 97, Folder 25)
- Morris, M.D., 1964-1982 (Box 97, Folder 26)
- Morrison Report, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 27)
- Motivation- "The Application of Academic & Motivational Variables to the Prediction of College Success in Engineering" by Thomas Kingsley, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 28)
- Moving Allowances, 1967-1980 (Box 97, Folder 29)
- Murphy, Peter J., 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 30)
- "N", 1959-1971 (Box 97, Folder 31)
- Nalco Chemical Company, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 32)
- NASA, 1966-1968 (Box 97, Folder 33)
- NASA, 1967-1972 (Box 97, Folder 34)
- NASA, 1962-1966 (Box 97, Folder 35)
- National Highway Safety Bureau, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 36)
- National Professions Foundation, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 37)
- National Academy of Sciences, 1957-1961 (Box 97, Folder 38)
- NACME- National Action Council for Minortities in Engineering. Inc., 1983-1988 (Box 97, Folder 39)
- National Bureau of Standards, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 40)
- National Cash Register, 1979-1984 (Box 97, Folder 41)
- National Engineering Laboratory Center for Chemical Engineering, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- National Mines (Subsidiary of National Steel), 1978-1980 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- NNF (National Nanofabrication Facility), 1987-1988 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- National Science Foundation, 1 July 1985 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Naval Research, Office of - Final Report, 1965-1970 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- National Heart Institute, 1969-1970 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Naval Research Lab (KOLB), 1966-1970 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- NBC, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Fluid-Network Analyzer, 1953-1956 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- NSF- Assoc Dean, 1966-1970 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- National Science Foundation, 1961-1973 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Nemhauser, George L., 1976-1986 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- New York State Accreditation, 1955-1958 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- New York University Center for Science & Technology Policy, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- New York State Education Department, 1972-1981 (Box 98, Folder 15)
- New York State Education Dept. Accreditation, 1967-1971 (Box 98, Folder 16)
- New York State Education Department, July 1, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- N.Y.S. Education Dept., 1 January 1968 - 1 October 1970 (Box 98, Folder 18)
- N.Y.S. Education Department and Engineering, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 19)
- NYS E & G Corp, 1976-1984 (Box 98, Folder 20)
- New York State Highway Project Joint Program: NYS Dept. of Public Works and Cornell University, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 21)
- N.Y.S. Scholarship Pretesting, 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 22)
- N.Y.S. Science & Tech Foundation Proposals, 1981-1985 (Box 98, Folder 23)
- N.Y.S. Transportation Study, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 24)
- New York Telephone Co. Publications, 1958-1962 (Box 98, Folder 25)
- New York Telephone Company Continuing Education, 1957-1964 (Box 98, Folder 26)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Co., 1971 (Box 98, Folder 27)
- Niehoff, Walter H. - Resume, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 28)
- NIPA Career Awards, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 29)
- Nowick, Arthur S., 1970 (Box 98, Folder 30)
- Nuclear Engineering Study Ad Hoc Committee, 1961-1966 (Box 98, Folder 31)
- Nuclear Reactor Lab, 1969-1972 (Box 98, Folder 32)
- Nuclear Science & Engineering, 1 July 1976 - 30 June 1981 (Box 98, Folder 33)
- Nuclear Science & Engineering, June 30, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 34)
- "O", 1958-1963 (Box 98, Folder 35)
- Olin Hall- Space Renovation, etc..., 1962-1974 (Box 98, Folder 36)
- Olsen, Tinius, 1977-1979 (Box 98, Folder 37)
- Ombudsman, 1971-1984 (Box 98, Folder 38)
- Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, School of, 1985-1986 (Box 98, Folder 39)
- Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, School of, 1984-1985 (Box 98, Folder 40)
- Executive Staff Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 98, Folder 41)
- Placement, Engineering, 1980-1984 (Box 98, Folder 42)
- Placement & Recruitment, Engineering to 6/30/80, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 43)
- Placement of Graduates, 1958-1963 (Box 98, Folder 44)
- Planning/Budgeting Priorities Group, 1981-1985 (Box 98, Folder 45)
- Teaching Awards, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Teaching Awards, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- College of Engineering Teaching Awards Nominations, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- College of Engineering Teaching Awards Nominations, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Plasma Studies, Lab for, July 1,1973-30 June 1978 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Plasma Studies, Lab for, 1972-1973 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Plasma Studies, Lab for, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Plasma Studies, Lab for, 1966-1969 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Plato IV System, 1973-1975 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Patents and Inventions, 1972-1984 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Pennysaver, Tri-Village Engineering Math Book, 1974-1975 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Perkins, James A, 1961-1969 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Peterson Guide, 1980-1982 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Pew Triangle Dedication, September 20, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Pew Proposals, July 1971-June 30, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Phoenix, S. Leigh, Associate Dean, July 1, 1986-May 30, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Phillips Hall, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Phillips Lounge Dedication, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- Pittsburgh Talk Re: Industry Comments, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Planning Facilities, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- Plasma Ad Hoc Group, 1965-1968 (Box 99, Folder 21)
- Plasma Studies, Laboratory of, July 1, 1978-June 30, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- Placement, Engineering, July 1, 1984-June 30 1988 (Box 99, Folder 23)
- Policy Committee Minutes, July 1, 1979-June 30, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 24)
- Policy Committee, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 25)
- Policy Committee (General), 1968-1973 (Box 99, Folder 26)
- Policy Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 99, Folder 27)
- Policy Committee (Legislation), 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 28)
- Policy Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 99, Folder 29)
- Policy Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 99, Folder 30)
- Policy Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 99, Folder 31)
- Postdoctoral Study, 1963-1971 (Box 99, Folder 32)
- Power- 1965 Buck Falls Conference (Box 99, Folder 33)
- Personnel, 1973-30 June 1982 (Box 99, Folder 34)
- Professional and Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on, 1968-1974 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Professional Engineers, National Society of, 1970-1988 (Box 100, Folder 2-3)
- Projection, 6-year, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Provost's Office (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - July 1, 1983-June 30, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - July 1, 1982-June 30, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - July 1, 1981-June 30, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 7-8)
  - July 1, 1979-June 30, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 9-10)
  - July 1, 1977-June 30, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 11-12)
- Operations Research and Ind Eng., July 1, 1981-June 30, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- Operations Research/Ind. Engineering School, July 1, 1977-June 30, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- Operations Research/Ind. Engineering School, July 1, 1973-June 30, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- Operations Research Dept., September 1967-June 1973 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Oral History, 1964-1970 (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Orientation, 1962-1979 (Box 100, Folder 18)
- P's - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 - 1969 (Box 100, Folder 19)
- Parents Letters, 1967-1970 (Box 100, Folder 20)
- Parents Weekend, 1960-1981 (Box 100, Folder 21)
- Parker-Hannafin Corp., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 22)
- Palumbo, Shelley - Academic Integrity Case, 1979-1980 (Box 100, Folder 23)
- Patent Disclosures, 1972-1975 (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Portrait - Dean Schultz, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 25)
- Power Engineering Proposal, 1960-1971 (Box 100, Folder 26-27)
- Power Scholarships, 1965-1966 (Box 100, Folder 28)
- Pre-Law Advisory Group, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 29)
- Pre-Med. & Pre-Dental Adv. Council, 1967-1973 (Box 100, Folder 30)
- PreRegistration, 1964-1967 (Box 100, Folder 31)
- President Rhodes Inauguration, November 10, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 32)
- Presidential Search Committee, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 33)
- President's Review, December 1966 (Box 100, Folder 34)
- Priority, Study, and Financial Plan - Report to President, July 1975 (Box 100, Folder 35)
- Provost's Office (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - July 1, 1975-June 30, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
  - October 1, 1969-June 30, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 3-4)
  - July 1, 1988-June 30, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 5-6)
  - July 1, 1987-June 30, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 7-8)
  - July 1, 1986-June 30, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - July 1, 1985-June 30, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 10-11)
  - July 1, 1984-June 30, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 12-13)
- Psychology Study Committee at C.U., 1969 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Public Policy, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Public Relations, 1964-1977 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Questionnaires and Surveys, 1979-1987 (Box 101, Folder 17-18)
- Quotas, 1965-1970 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- R's - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950 -1969 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Radiophyscis A.I.O. Cable, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- Recruiting (Munschauer), 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- Regents Master Plan, 1972-1974 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- Regional History and University Archives, 1959 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Regional Resources and Development (Box 101, Folder 25)
- Regional Studies, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Registration, 1957-1963 (Box 101, Folder 27)
- Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1982-1985 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- Resler Engine, 1973-1976 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- ROTC, 1963-1979 (Box 101, Folder 30)
- RPI Cooperation (Dean A.A.Burr), 1963-1980 (Box 101, Folder 31)
- RPI Cooperation Reports and Proposals, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 32)
- Rudolph Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 33)
- Rural Development Advisory Council, 1973-1978 (Box 101, Folder 34)
- Rural Development Advisory Council, July 1973-June 20, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 1)